{
    "title": "Know Your City",
    "category" : {
        "park": [
            {
                "question" : "Know about park with skating arena?",
                "answer" : ["Central Park", "Bryant Park"]
            },
            {
                "question" : "Know about park with water activities?",
                "answer" : ["Central Park"]
            },
            {
                "question" : "Know about park with picnic area?",
                "answer" : ["Central Park"]
            } ,
            {
                "question" : "Know about park with library?",
                "answer" : ["Bryant Park"]
            },
            {
                "question" : "Know about park with running activities?",
                "answer" : ["Central Park"]
            }                                                
        ],
        "architecture": [
            {
                "question": "Know about historical architecture?",
                "answer" : ["NYC Library"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about modern architecture?",
                "answer" : ["WTC"]
            }            
        ],
        "monuments": [
            {
                "question": "Know about historical monuments?",
                "answer" : ["Statue of Liberty", "Brooklyn Bridge"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about historical monuments?",
                "answer" : ["Statue of Liberty", "Brooklyn Bridge"]
            }                      
        ],
        "mueseums": [
            {
                "question": "Know about contemporary mueseums?",
                "answer" : ["The Metropolitan Museum of Art", "Museum of Modern Art"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about science mueseums?",
                "answer" :["American Museum of Natural History", "Intrepid Sea, Air & Space Museum"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about history mueseums?",
                "answer" : ["The New-York Historical Society", "The Metropolitan Museum of Art"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about kids mueseums?",
                "answer" : ["Brooklyn Children's Museum", "NYC Transit Museum", "NYC Fire Museum"]
            }
        ],
        "cruises" : [
            {
                "question": "Know about party cruises?",
                "answer" : ["Empire Cruises", "Hornblower Cruises"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about city tour cruises?",
                "answer" : ["Circle Line Sightseeing", "City Sightseeing"]
            } 
        ],
        "food": [
            {
                "question": "Know about Italian Restaurant?",
                "answer" : ["rubirosa"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about American Dinners?",
                "answer" : ["The Dutch", "Estela"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about Chinese Restaurant?",
                "answer" : ["Atlas Kitchen", "108 Food- Dried Hot Pot"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Know about Indian Restaurant?",
                "answer" : ["Usha Foods", "Junoon", "Adda"]
            }                        
        ]
    }
}